<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.kdiff3.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KDiff3</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KDiff3</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KDiff3</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KDiff3</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">KDiff3</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KDiff3</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KDiff3</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">KDiff3</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">KDiff3</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">KDiff3</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">KDiff3</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KDiff3</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KDiff3</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">KDiff3</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KDiff3</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Kdiff3</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KDiff3</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKDiff3xx</name>
  <summary>A File And Directory Comparison And Merge Tool</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Una eina per a comparar i fusionar directoris i fitxers</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Una eina per a comparar i fusionar directoris i fitxers</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Nástroj pro porovnávání a slučování souborů a adresářů</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Programm zum Vergleichen und Zusammenführen von Dateien und Ordnern</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">A File And Directory Comparison And Merge Tool</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Una herramienta para comparar y fusionar archivos y directorios</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Tiedostojen ja kansioiden vertailu- ja yhdistämistyökalu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Un outil de comparaison et de fusion de fichiers et de dossiers</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Unha ferramenta de comparación e fusión de ficheiros e directorios</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Uno strumento di confronto e di fusione di file e cartelle</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Een hulpmiddel voor het vergelijken en samenvoegen van bestanden en mappen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Uma Ferramenta de Comparação e Junção de Pastas e Ficheiros</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Nástroj na porovnanie a zlúčenie súborov a adresárov</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Ett verktyg för jämförelse och sammanfogning av filer och kataloger</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Програма для порівняння і об'єднання файлів та каталогів</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxA File And Directory Comparison And Merge Toolxx</summary>
  <url type="homepage">https://gitlab.com/tfischer/kdiff3</url>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <description>
    <p>KDiff3 is a file and directory diff and merge tool which</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KDiff3 és una eina per a la comparació i fusionat de fitxers i directoris</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El KDiff3 és una eina per a la comparació i fusionat de fitxers i directoris</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">KDiff3 is a file and directory diff and merge tool which</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Kdiff3 on tiedostojen ja kansioiden vertailu- ja yhdistämistyökalu, joka:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">KDiff3 est un outil de comparaison et de fusion de fichiers et de dossiers qui</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">KDiff3 è uno strumento per fondere file e cartelle che</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KDdiff3 is een hulpmiddel om bestanden en mappen te vergelijken en samen te voegen dat</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KDiff3 é uma ferramenta de detecção e junção das diferenças entre ficheiros e pastas que</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Kdiff3 är ett verktyg för jämförelse och sammanfogning av filer och kataloger, som</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KDiff3 — програма для визначення відмінностей у файлах і каталогах та об'єднання цих відмінностей в один варіант, яка</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKDiff3 is a file and directory diff and merge tool whichxx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>compares and merges two or three text input files or directories,</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">compara i fusiona dos o tres fitxers o directoris des de l'entrada,</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">compara i fusiona dos o tres fitxers o directoris des de l'entrada,</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">compares and merges two or three text input files or directories,</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">vertaa kahta tai kolmea tekstitiedostoa tai kansiota ja osaa yhdistää ne</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">compare et fusionne deux ou trois fichiers ou dossiers en entrée,</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">confronta e fonde due o tre file di testo o cartelle in ingresso,</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">twee of drie tekstbestanden of mappen vergelijkt en samenvoegt,</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">compara e junta dois ou três ficheiros de texto ou pastas de entrada,</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">jämför och sammanfogar två eller tre textfiler eller kataloger,</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">порівнює і об’єднує два або три вхідних текстових файлів або каталогів.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxcompares and merges two or three text input files or directories,xx</li>
      <li>shows the differences line by line and character by character(!),</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">mostra les diferències línia per línia i caràcter per caràcter!,</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">mostra les diferències línia per línia i caràcter per caràcter!,</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">shows the differences line by line and character by character(!),</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">näyttää erot riveittäin ja merkeittäin (!)</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">affiche les différences ligne par ligne et caractère par caractère (!),</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">mostra le differenze riga per riga e carattere per carattere(!),</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">toont de verschillen regel voor regel en teken voor teken(!),</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">mostra as diferenças linha-a-linha e carácter-a-carácter(!),</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">visar skillnaderna rad för rad och tecken för tecken (!),</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">показує відмінності за рядками і за символами(!),</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxshows the differences line by line and character by character(!),xx</li>
      <li>provides an automatic merge-facility,</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">proporciona la facilitat del fusionat automàtic,</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">proporciona la facilitat del fusionat automàtic,</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">provides an automatic merge-facility,</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">tarjoaa automaattisen yhdistämistoiminnon</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">offre des fonctionnalités de fusion automatique,</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">fornisce un servizio automatico per la fusione,</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">een automatische samenvoegfunctie biedt,</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">oferece uma funcionalidade de junção automática,</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">tillhandahåller en automatisk sammanfogingsfunktion,</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">надає можливість автоматичного об’єднання,</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxprovides an automatic merge-facility,xx</li>
      <li>has an editor for comfortable solving of merge-conflicts,</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">té un editor per a la solució còmoda dels conflictes de fusionat,</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">té un editor per a la solució còmoda dels conflictes de fusionat,</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">has an editor for comfortable solving of merge-conflicts,</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">sisältää muokkaimen yhdistämisristiriitojen ratkaisemiseksi</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">dispose d'un éditeur pour résoudre confortablement les conflits lors de la fusion,</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">dispone di un editor per risolvere comodamente i conflitti di fusione,</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">een editor heeft voor het comfortabel oplossen van samenvoegconflicten,</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">tem um editor para resolver confortavelmente os conflitos de junção,</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">har en editor för bekväm lösning av sammanfogningskonflikter,</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">містить редактор для полегшення розв’язання конфліктів під час об’єднання,</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxhas an editor for comfortable solving of merge-conflicts,xx</li>
      <li>provides network transparency via KIO,</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">proporciona transparència de xarxa a través del KIO,</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">proporciona transparència de xarxa a través del KIO,</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">provides network transparency via KIO,</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">tarjoaa läpinäkyvän verkon KIOn kautta</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">fournit une transparence réseau via KIO,</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">fornisce trasparenza di rete tramite KIO,</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">netwerktransparantie biedt via KIO,</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">oferece a transparência na rede com o KIO,</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">tillhandahåller nätverkstransparens via KIO,</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">забезпечує мережеву прозорість за допомогою KIO,</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxprovides network transparency via KIO,xx</li>
      <li>has options to highlight or hide changes in white-space or comments,</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">té opcions per a ressaltar o ocultar els canvis en els espais en blanc o els comentaris,</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">té opcions per a ressaltar o ocultar els canvis en els espais en blanc o els comentaris,</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">has options to highlight or hide changes in white-space or comments,</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">osaa korostaa tai piilottaa muutokset tyhjemerkeissä ja kommenteissa</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">dispose d'options permettant de surligner ou de cacher les différences d'espaces ou de commentaires,</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">ha opzioni per evidenziare o per nascondere le modifiche negli spazi o nei commenti,</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">opties heeft voor het accentueren of verbergen van wijzigingen in witruimte of commentaar,</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">tem opções para realçar ou esconder as alterações nos espaços em branco ou comentários,</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">har alternativ för att markera eller dölja ändringar av blanktecken eller kommentarer,</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">може підсвічувати або ховати зміни у пробілах або коментарях,</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxhas options to highlight or hide changes in white-space or comments,xx</li>
      <li>supports Unicode, UTF-8 and other file encodings,</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">admet Unicode, UTF-8 i altres codificacions de fitxer,</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">admet Unicode, UTF-8 i altres codificacions de fitxer,</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">podporuje Unicode, UTF-8 a další kódování souborů.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">supports Unicode, UTF-8 and other file encodings,</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">tukee Unicodea, UTF-8:aa ja muita merkistökoodauksia</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">prend en charge Unicode, UTF-8 et d'autres encodages de fichiers,</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">supporta Unicode, UTF-8 e altre codifiche di file,</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Unicode, UTF-8 en andere bestandscoderingen ondersteunt,</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">suporta o Unicode, o UTF-8 e outras codificações de ficheiros,</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">stöder Unicode, UTF-8 och andra filkodningar,</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">підтримує Unicode, UTF-8 та інші кодування текстів файлів,</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxsupports Unicode, UTF-8 and other file encodings,xx</li>
      <li>prints differences,</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">imprimeix les diferències,</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">imprimeix les diferències,</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">prints differences,</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">tulostaa eroavuudet</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">affiche les différences,</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">stampa le differenze,</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">verschillen in regels afdrukt,</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">imprime as diferenças,</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">skriver ut skillnader,</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">може надсилати на друк різницю,</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxprints differences,xx</li>
      <li>supports version control keyword and history merging.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">admet la paraula clau per al control de versions i un historial de les fusions.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">admet la paraula clau per al control de versions i un historial de les fusions.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">supports version control keyword and history merging.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">tukee versionhallinnan avainsanoja ja historian yhdistämistä.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">prend en charge les mots clés de contrôle de version et la fusion des historiques.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">supporta le parole chiave per il controllo di versione e la fusione della cronologia.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">versiebeheersleutelwoorden ondersteunt en samenvoegen van geschiedenis.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">suporta as palavras-chave de controlo de versões e de junção do histórico.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">stöder nyckelord för versionskontroll och sammanfogning av historik.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">підтримує об’єднання за ключовими словами і журналом інструментів керування версіями.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxsupports version control keyword and history merging.xx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <provides>
    <binary>kdiff3</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
